Shrishti Yaday

Anywhere

shrishtiyadav65 2py@indeedemail.com

+91-8619006326

A Mental Health Professional, with a Master's in Applied Psychology, who discovered having good inter and intra-personal skills in the final year of B.tech. Academically average, but an all-rounder, who

participates in organizing and managing events.. Also, have taken up leadership roles and worked remarkably well in

those positions. A self-initiator, who finds new ways to be more effective and to do better for the environment, in the best way possible.

Competencies:

- Leadership
- Awareness
- Adaptability
- Communication
- Empathy
- Flexibility
- Approachability
- Team Work

#readytowork

Work Experience

School Counselor

Sophia Girls Sr. Sec School January 2020 to Present

part-time role, visiting the school three days a week.

Consultant Counselor

Yourdost

October 2019 to Present

part-time role, in which I have been mentoring the learners under PMKVY.

Life skills trainer

Quality Education Asia July 2019 to September 2019

Conducted training sessions for the students from two schools of classes 6th-10th on various topics of life skills.

Counseling Internship under Dr. Kavita Bhargava, Counsellor and Psychotherapist

Emotional Intelligence, Resilience and Workoholism among Doctors August 2018 to May 2019

Aug'18- May'19)

• Counseling Internship under Dr. Kavita Bhargava, Counsellor and Psychotherapist at EHCC hospital

Placement Coordinator

University Level Recognition 2019 to 2019

Organized and managed various events (Departmental as well as University level) during B.tech.

Class Representative of MA Applied Psychology

University Level Recognition 2017 to 2019

Awarded by Baljeet Shastri Award (University Level Recognition)

Internship

Educational Research January 2018 to March 2018

Internship in Psycho-Oncology

Dr. Puneet Gupta August 2017 to October 2017

Extra Co-Curricular Activities:

Education

M.A in Applied Psychology

Amity University - Noida, Uttar Pradesh 2019

B.tech

(Electrical and Electronics Engineering) VIT university - Vellore, Tamil Nadu 2013

CBSE in BOARD

St. Paul Secondary School - Pratapgarh, Rajasthan 2011

Skills / IT Skills

• managerial skills, Coordination, documentation

Online Profile

https://www.linkedin.com/in/shrishti-yadav-72b671b6